(The characters, locations, organizations and events in the play are purely fictitious)
（剧中人物、地点、组织、事件纯属虚构）
Who are you?
你是谁？
How come you have this watch?
你怎么会有这块手表？
I heard that Taihu would die if he messed around with you.
听说太虎要是惹你就会死。
Taihu never said he had a cousin
太湖从来没有说过他有一个表弟
Have you found Taihu's murderer?
找到太湖的凶手了吗？
Is this what you came here to ask about?
你来这里就是想问这个吗？
We are also looking for someone
我们也在找人
That's enough
够了
What did you just say?
你刚刚说什么？
Really
真的
Don't do anything
不要做任何事
Why do you suddenly want to find Taihu when you have nothing to do?
为什么没事的时候突然想去找太湖呢？
none of your business
关你屁事
What the hell are you doing?
你到底在做什么？
My friend died
我的朋友死了
Just looking at you bunch of losers makes me angry.
光是看着你们这群失败者就让我生气。
Goddamn
该死的
how?
如何？
Are you really Taihu’s friends?
你真的是太湖的朋友吗？
Yes or no?
是还是不是？
What else are you scum doing?
你这渣渣还干什么？
Is it right?
这样对吗？
where are you going?
你要去哪里？
Of course we are looking for the bastard who killed Taihu.
我们当然是在寻找杀死太湖的混蛋。
Then what?
然后呢？
Cut him into pieces
将他切成碎片
Come to my office another day
改天来我办公室吧
Let’s talk about Taihu
说说太湖吧
go away
离开
Do you really want to let him go like this?
你真的要就这样放过他吗？
How about it?
这个怎么样？
He asked me to go to his office
他让我去他的办公室
Yeah?
是的？
I acted very well
我演得很好
Fool
傻子
"Evil of Evils"
《恶中之恶》
I went to see Taihu last week
上周我去看了太湖
The new tower is well maintained
新塔维护得很好
makes me very happy
让我很高兴
correct
正确的
Why didn't Taihu mention that he had a cousin?
太湖为何不提自己有一个表弟？
Why don't you keep your gold watch?
你为什么不保留你的金表？
What should I do with a gold retention watch?
黄金保留手表该怎么办？
I didn’t see half of their photos together
我没看到他们在一起的一半照片
Chenghao…
Chenghao…
There was no news about him after he went to work as a fisherman.
他去打渔后就再也没有他的消息了。
He recently came back and asked me about Taihu
他最近回来问我关于太湖的事
My brother lives in Wonju
我哥哥住在原州
When Taihu was in primary school
太湖上小学的时候
Every summer, I go to Wonju to find Chenghao.
每年夏天，我都会去原州寻找成浩。
They stick together all day like twins
他们像双胞胎一样整天粘在一起
It is conceivable
这是可以想象的
How shocked was he when he heard the news of Taihu's death?
当他听到太湖去世的消息时，有多么震惊？
(Anti-Narcotics Division Shi Daoheng)
（缉毒科石道恒）
I haven't used half of the money you gave me.
你给我的钱我还没用完一半。
Take the money and leave
拿了钱就走
besides…
除了…
Don't come back again
不要再回来
When I see you, I think of Taihu
看到你我就想起太湖
will make me hate you
会让我恨你
The variable in the mission is that they may find Taihu's father
任务的变数是他们可能会找到太湖的父亲
Ask me something
问我一些事
Please get ready
请做好准备
(Karaoke bar, massage)
(卡拉 OK 吧、按摩)
(Zheng Qitie)
(Zheng Qitie)
Those little punks
那些小混混们
Hello
你好
Don't just stand, come and sit
不要只是站着，过来坐下
I am always thinking
我总是在想
A cousin with whom I had no contact suddenly appeared
一个和我没有联系的表弟突然出现
Noisy restaurant
吵闹的餐厅
What do you think the situation is?
您认为情况如何？
I see through your intentions
我看穿你的意图
take it
拿去
Stop using his name to scam money.
别再用他的名字来骗钱了。
Even if you are his cousin, my patience has limits
就算你是他表弟，我的忍耐也是有限度的
Take the money and get out
拿了钱就出去
You scumbags are really just hooligans
你们这些人渣其实就是流氓而已
What did you say?
你说什么？
Do you think
你认为
Will I be happy if I just take the money and leave?
如果我拿了钱就走我会高兴吗？
Son of a bitch
王八蛋
do not get excited
别激动
I can't stand it, come here
我受不了了，过来吧
-Please... -How?
-拜托...- 怎么样？
You can't stand it? Come if you have the guts
你受不了吗？如果你有胆量就来吧
Want to know what happens next?
想知道接下来会发生什么吗？
Fuck you, second-rate gangster.
去你妈的，二流流氓。
Real or fake, are you blocking me again?
是真的还是假的，你又屏蔽我了吗？
Go away, asshole
走开，混蛋
Don't do it all, idiot
别做这一切，白痴
We are not punks
我们不是朋克
Longda
Longda
yes
是的
go to hell
去死吧
Son of a bitch
王八蛋
hateful
可恶
Damn thing
该死的东西
Everyone clean up
大家都清理干净
yes
是的
What are you talking about?
你在说什么？
Who kicked me just now?
刚才是谁踢了我？
asshole
混蛋
come down
坠落
Kick you to death
一脚踢死你
Son of a bitch
王八蛋
Flesh feet
肉脚
useless waste
无用的废物
asshole
混蛋
Damn it
该死的
Go to hell
去死吧
Let me go, asshole
放开我吧混蛋
Damn thing
该死的东西
scrap material
废料
you this…
你这个……
little waste
浪费很少
enough
足够的
I don’t think you’re here to cheat money.
我不认为你是来骗钱的。
Son of a bitch
王八蛋
listen to me
听我说
When my uncle helped me put on Taihu’s watch,
当叔叔帮我戴上太湖表时，
Do you know what he said?
你知道他说了什么吗？
He said wearing this watch feels like Taihu is with him
他说戴上这款手表感觉太湖就在他身边
don't take revenge
不要报复
But you know what?
但你知道吗？
Thank you Taihu for treating you as friends
谢谢太湖把你们当朋友
I really feel sorry for him
我真的很对不起他
I…
我…
He will avenge Taihu at all costs
他会不惜一切代价为太湖报仇
You guys are a bunch of bastards
你们就是一群混蛋
Just clean this place and stay here
只需清理这个地方并留在这里
I will find the murderer
我会找到凶手
bring his head
带上他的头
A bunch of unloyal bastards
一群不忠的混蛋
His name is Quan Chenghao?
His name is Quan Chenghao?
Yes, how?
是啊，怎么办？
Do you want to join him?
你想加入他吗？
Just treat it as the reincarnation of Taihu
就当作太湖转世吧
What are you talking about?
你在说什么？
You also saw that he is good at fighting.
你也看到了，他很擅长战斗。
One more person like Brother Xu
又一个像徐哥一样的人
Wouldn’t it be nice to have a strong thug?
拥有一个强大的暴徒不是很好吗？
How can you trust him?
你怎么能相信他？
He said he was Taihu’s cousin
他说他是太湖的表弟
Nishinari
西成
When did you trust people so easily?
你什么时候这么容易相信人了？
Stop making trouble
别再惹麻烦了
What did you say?
你说什么？
you know what I mean
你知道我的意思
Our business is not simple
我们的生意并不简单
It's better to be careful
最好还是小心一点
Stop being so brainless
别再这么无脑了
No matter how big or small the guy is
不管这个家伙有多大或多小
You love to pick on me lately
你最近很爱欺负我
Otherwise, what else is there to find? damn it
不然还有什么可找的呢？该死的
damn it?
该死的？
Go do something quickly
快点去做某事
Okay, whatever you want to do
好吧，无论你想做什么
Hello, have you seen this person?
你好，你见过这个人吗？
-Hello
-你好
Have you ever seen…
你有没有见过…
Wasn't it great yesterday? Super cool
昨天不是很棒吗？超酷
yesterday…
昨天…
how?
如何？
Isn’t that Quan Chenghao?
那不是权成浩吗？
That bastard
那个混蛋
-what? Don't pull me - forget it
-什么？别拉我 ——忘了吧
follow me
跟我来
-Boss -Hello
-老板 -你好
What did he just ask you?
他刚才问你什么？
Ask me if I have ever seen this person
问我是否见过这个人
(Wanted murder suspect)
（通缉谋杀嫌疑人）
- Call the police if you see him. - Please give me a bowl of soup.
- 如果你看到他就报警。 - 请给我一碗汤。
-thank you -go
-谢谢你 -去
goodbye
再见
Hello
你好
Have you ever seen this person?
你见过这个人吗？
If you see him please call the police
如果你看到他请报警
That bastard
那个混蛋
Please call the police, thank you
请报警，谢谢
(Busan, South Korea)
（韩国釜山）
- Give it to me - Yes, boss.
- 给我 - 是的，老板。
very good
非常好
Take it for lunch
拿它当午餐
Thank you boss
谢谢老板
Walk
走
haven't seen you for a long time
好久没见到你了
asshole
混蛋
Son of a bitch
王八蛋
Wait a moment
稍等
Calm down and listen to me
冷静下来，听我说
I came here without telling Qi Tie
我没有告诉齐铁就来到这里
I have something important
我有重要的事
I hit it off with you
我和你一拍即合
I really wish we were friends
我真的希望我们是朋友
But at that time, classes were clearly defined
但那时候阶级是明确的
I'm talking about you
我正在谈论你
If you have something to say, say it directly and don't talk in circles.
有话要说就直接说，不要绕圈子。
After listening to this, I will see if I want to stab you with this knife.
听完我就看我要不要用这把刀刺你。
Have you heard the rumors in the world?
你听过世界上的谣言吗？
Is Qitie making a fortune recently?
七贴最近发财了吗？
Don't ask around, just fart quickly
别问周围，快放个屁
He sends tens of millions in cash to the boss every month
他每个月都会给老板寄几千万现金
Think about how much he actually makes
想想他实际赚了多少钱
He will become arrogant after making a little money
赚了一点钱就会变得嚣张
Now he looks down on people
现在他看不起人
Thinking you are superior
认为自己很优秀
We have been friends for ten years, and he calls me back and forth
我们做了十年的朋友，他经常给我打电话
Poor waste
可怜的废物
So embarrassing
好尴尬
Han Tu
韩土
Let's work together to get rid of Qi Tie
让我们齐心协力除掉齐铁
You have a chance to take it back domineeringly
你还有机会霸气夺回来
previous territory
以前的领土
We discouraged him so he couldn't work
我们劝阻他，让他无法工作
Take away his business
抢走他的生意
I am familiar with all operations
我熟悉所有操作
useless things
无用的东西
You came all the way to betray your friends?
你千里迢迢跑来就是为了背叛你的朋友吗？
We didn't have a wedding and my girlfriend is eight months pregnant
我们没有举行婚礼，我女朋友已经怀孕八个月了
I want to support my family, don’t people need to have great ambitions?
我要养家糊口，人不需要有远大的志向吗？
You can ask the boss first
你可以先问老板
Gather the old Busan gang again
釜山老帮再次集结
Then I will take care of the Jiangnan side
那我就照顾江南那边
It shouldn't be difficult
应该不难
To leave a message please press two
留言请按二
Please leave a message
请留言
Yi-jeong, I’m in Daegu
伊贞，我在大邱
A murder suspect fled here
一名杀人嫌疑人逃到这里
I'm going to stay and watch him until I catch him.
我会留下来看着他，直到抓住他。
don't worry too much
别太担心
I will leave another message
我会再留言
Why so slow?
为什么这么慢？
Traffic jam on the road
路上堵车
Pour me a drink
给我倒杯饮料
Please nod, we promise not to fail
请点头，我们保证不会失败
We are direct descendants of the gang
我们是这个团伙的直系后裔
They are just street gangsters from Jiangnan
他们只是江南的街头混混
There's no need to get angry over a few street gangsters
没必要为了几个街头小混混而生气
You are born stupid
你生来就是傻子
Or were you being particularly stupid that day?
还是那天你特别蠢？
You are your direct descendants, right?
你是你的直系后裔吧？
Qitie sends me money on time every month
七贴每个月都会按时给我寄钱
My Japanese sworn brothers also admire him
我的日本结拜兄弟也很佩服他
Said no one was allowed to touch him
说不准任何人碰他
to be honest
说实话
You take over that area
你接管那个区域
It doesn't make much difference to me
这对我来说没有多大区别
You know Hong Xicheng, right?
你认识洪熙成吧？
He is one of ours now, he will definitely get it done this time
他现在是我们的一员了，这次他一定能完成任务
You let us take over Jiangnan
你让我们占领江南
We give you twice the money every month
我们每个月给你双倍的钱
Zheng Qitie
Zheng Qitie
(Zheng Qitie)
(Zheng Qitie)
I'm Zheng Qitie, come out and meet me
我是郑七铁，出来见我吧
Wasn't there a rock and roll nightclub here before?
这里以前不是有一家摇滚夜总会吗？
It was left empty when it went bankrupt, and we later took it over.
它破产后就空置了，后来我们接手了。
Qitie said that this area needs more young people to drive business
齐铁说，这个地区需要更多年轻人来带动生意
He plans to open a new nightclub
他计划开一家新的夜总会
That stupid DJ really loves to dance and have carnivals
那个愚蠢的DJ真的很喜欢跳舞和狂欢
Every time you sign a contract
每次签订合同时
It is our tradition to celebrate together
一起庆祝是我们的传统
Just tonight
只是今晚
Is everything ready?
一切准备好了吗？
certainly
当然
Guaranteed to be foolproof
保证万无一失
The younger brother hid in three motels
弟弟躲进三间汽车旅馆
wait until the time is right
等到时机成熟
They'll rush in in droves
他们会成群结队地涌来
To deceive others
去欺骗别人
Only one person can lead a guy, right?
只有一个人才能领导一个人，对吗？
certainly
当然
Or should I bring the guy in first?
还是我应该先带那家伙进来？
What about hiding them inside?
把它们藏在里面怎么样？
That's fine if you want
如果你愿意的话没问题
Listen
听
There is a small bar near the stage
舞台附近有一个小酒吧
I'll put the weapons down there
我会把武器放在那里
good
好的
And one more thing
还有一件事
What's up?
这是怎么回事？
They are all my brothers
他们都是我的兄弟
please
请
Don't be too harsh
别太严厉
Don't kill anyone
不要杀任何人
What words?
什么话？
That depends on how you arrange it
这取决于你如何安排
We have no way to guarantee
我们没有办法保证
drive
驾驶
yes
是的
What are you doing?
你在干什么？
Han Tu, please
韩图，请
You've found the right place
您找到了正确的地方
What is this place?
这是什么地方？
What tricks do you want to play?
你想玩什么花样？
We're going to party here tonight
今晚我们要在这里聚会
In memory of Taihu
纪念太湖
I don't have time to listen to your nonsense
我没时间听你废话
carnival?
狂欢？
I heard you are looking for Taihu’s murderer
听说你正在寻找杀害太湖的凶手
Keep the change, please
不用找了
join my gang
加入我的帮派
I only opened my mouth because you are Taihu’s cousin.
我张开嘴只是因为你是太湖的表弟。
Want me to join your gang?
要我加入你们的帮派吗？
Yeah?
是的？
Then who wants to avenge Taihu?
那谁要为太湖报仇呢？
Let's go
我们走吧
Qitie
Qitie
who are they?
他们是谁？
Brother Zhang killed Taihu, those are his people
张哥杀了太湖，那是他的人
Where is the party going?
聚会要去哪里？
That bastard Xicheng
西城那个混蛋
Han Tu
韩土
damn it
该死的
Seize Qitie
Seize Qitie
beat them to death
把他们打死
Son of a bitch
王八蛋
waste
浪费
Get that bastard, you loser
抓住那个混蛋，你这个失败者
go to hell
去死吧
asshole
混蛋
Who is this brat?
这小子是谁？
That bastard...get up
这混蛋……起来吧
hurry up
赶快
Good night
晚安
Are you annoyed?
烦到你了吗？
kill them all
杀光他们
Kill
杀
Offal
内脏
Son of a bitch
王八蛋
waste
浪费
-I'm going to beat you to death -That's enough
-我要把你打死 -够了
You choose
你选
I'm going to die here
我会死在这里
Or don't let me see you again?
还是不要让我再见到你？
tidy up
整理
I have no strength left, call it a day.
我已经没有力气了，今天就到此为止吧。
Do not touch me
不要碰我
Let it go, asshole
放开吧，混蛋
take your hands away
把你的手拿开
Told you not to touch me, you damn bastard
告诉过你不要碰我，你这个该死的混蛋
let me go
让我走
Han Tu
韩土
- let me go - bastard
-放开我 -混蛋
Han Tu
韩土
Walk slowly without seeing anyone off
慢慢地走，不送别任何人
asshole
混蛋
friend
朋友
Get lost, asshole
滚蛋吧，混蛋
I see you were beaten badly
我看你被打得很惨
Jiangnan is our home
江南是我们的家
Don't come again
别再来了
sorry
对不起
asshole
混蛋
- Han Tu, he's leaving - bastard
- 韩土，他要走了 - 混蛋
Don't come to our territory again, you country bumpkin.
你这个土包子，别再来我们的地盘了。
The blood stains are all gone. Wipe them off quickly.
血迹全部消失了。赶紧把它们擦掉。
-Jae Hoon -very good
-Jae Hoon - 非常好
- mop it off - good
- 把它擦掉 - 很好
- do things quickly - yes
- 快速做事 - 是的
As expected, you expected it
正如你所预料的那样
They all took the bait
他们都上钩了
Thanks
谢谢
-Han Tu... -Just asking out of curiosity
-韩图... -只是出于好奇才问
Why did you call me here?
你为什么叫我来这里？
Force me to fight?
逼我打架？
Would you like to tell him personally?
你愿意亲自告诉他吗？
Yes, boss
是的，老板
I am Zheng Qitie
I am Zheng Qitie
So annoying
很烦人
I heard that you nodded to Brother Zhang’s younger brother
听说你向张哥的弟弟点了点头
sneak attack on me
偷袭我
It’s a shame that I gave you so much money
可惜我给了你这么多钱
Isn't this very kind?
这不是很贴心吗？
I will never send money there again.
我再也不会寄钱到那里了。
Take care of yourself
照顾好你自己
Go to Seoul and find Zheng Qitie
去首尔找郑其铁
Cut open his intestines and throw him into the sea of ​​Incheon
切开他的肠子，把他扔进仁川海里
No, wait
不，等等
Capture him, disembowel him in Busan, disembowel him and throw him into the sea
抓住他，在釜山把他开膛破肚，把他开膛破肚扔进海里
one way or another
不管怎样
Should I contact you?
我应该联系你吗？
Kanemoto Rodai?
金本路大？
You must be good at acting
你的演技一定很好
Only those bastards in Busan would believe it
只有釜山那些混蛋才会相信
I want to get rid of the useless parasites in the gang
我要除掉帮派里那些无用的寄生虫
Just use a trick within a trick
只用一招中的一招
There's a good reason for everything here
这里的一切都有充分的理由
So what?
所以呢？
It's not my business?
不关我的事？
Where is Brother Zhang?
张弟兄在哪里？
Brother, it's all done
兄弟，一切都完成了
Let’s talk after we go out
出去之后再说吧
yes
是的
lit
点亮
(Taihu Rock Cafe)
(Taihu Rock Cafe)
Taihu wanted to open a shop here during his lifetime
太湖生前就想在这里开店
It should have opened earlier, no one is here now
应该早点开门的，现在没人了
Too tiger…
太虎了……
like my brother
像我兄弟一样
I want you to help him fulfill his last wish
我要你帮他完成他最后的愿望
i killed him
我杀了他
That bastard Brother Zhang killed Taihu
张哥那个混蛋杀了太湖
I chopped him into mincemeat
我把他剁成肉末
My name is Quan Chenghao. Please give me your advice.
我叫全成浩。请给我你的建议。
Those who were dissatisfied with him are now wiped out
那些对他不满的人现在都被消灭了
He is the most junior, so he should be nicer to others, you know?
他年纪最小，应该对别人好一点，知道吗？
-yes
-是的
do you know?
你知道吗？
yes
是的
applause
掌声
About Hyeon-dong and Yeoksam-dong
关于贤洞和驿三洞
Only these two areas belong to us
只有这两个区域是属于我们的
Can't cross the line
不能越线
There is a boss in every district
每个区都有一个老板
The job of the newcomer is to patrol the territory
新人的工作是巡逻领地
From five o'clock in the evening to five o'clock the next morning
从晚上五点到第二天早上五点
like a patrolman
像巡警一样
Check to see if there are any accidents or if anyone is causing trouble
检查是否发生事故或有人制造麻烦
When you see people from other gangs, report it immediately, that's it
看到其他帮派的人，立即举报，就这样了
Do you understand?
你明白吗？
Turn left over there
那边左转
By the way, why are you speaking so politely to me?
顺便问一下，你为什么对我说话这么客气？
I'm very polite to anyone who can fight.
我对任何能战斗的人都非常有礼貌。
I've seen your skills
我见过你的技能
Even Jackie Chan and Bruce Lee have to bow down.
就连成龙、李小龙也不得不跪拜。
You are awesome
你太棒了
Fight well
好好战斗
Do you want to learn Taekwondo?
你想学跆拳道吗？
-Are you sick? -Who are you?
-你生病了吗？ -你是谁？
I have the guts to fight
我有勇气去战斗
Son of a bitch
王八蛋
What's wrong with you?
你这人怎么回事？
Don't be impulsive
不要冲动
Damn thing
该死的东西
- That bastard - let's go, let's go
-那个混蛋 -我们走吧，我们走
What did you say?
你说什么？
Good night
晚安
Hello boss
你好老板
Long Da, keep up the good work
龙达，继续努力
How long will we be patrolling the streets like this?
我们还要这样在街上巡逻多久？
We don't have to patrol the streets until new people arrive.
在新人到来之前我们不必在街上巡逻。
When was that?
那是什么时候？
After graduating from high school
高中毕业后
It will take some time
需要一些时间
Hello
你好
-Hello, big brother -Longda
-你好，大哥 -龙达
yes
是的
do things well
把事情做好
do you know?
你知道吗？
Good night
晚安
it hurts
好痛
If you stay undercover until the end
如果你一直卧底到最后
What if driving skills only get better?
如果驾驶技术只会变得更好怎么办？
who knows
谁知道
I need to take a nap, call me later
我要睡一觉，稍后再给我打电话
I have to patrol the streets again
我又得上街巡逻了
Most gangs charge so-called protection fees
大多数帮派收取所谓的保护费
Each of our members runs a store
我们的每个会员都经营一家商店
Half of the profits are turned over to the company
一半利润上缴公司
The system is quite advanced
系统相当先进
Do you sell catering or anything else?
你们卖餐饮还是其他什么？
Something else? what?
还有别的事吗？什么？
Gambling or other business
赌博或其他业务
You are the best in the gang, I am the second best
你是队里最好的，我是第二好的
How could I know
我怎么知道
I only know which nightclub has hot girls
我只知道哪个夜店有辣妹
(Seoul Provincial Police Agency, South Korea)
（韩国首尔地方警察厅）
(Security Division)
（保安科）
Mr. Cha Fengzhu
Mr. Cha Fengzhu
If you violate the National Security Law, you will face three to five years in prison.
如果违反国家安全法，将面临三到五年的监禁。
Will be kicked out of university
将会被大学开除
You will also have a criminal record when you go out to find a job.
你出去找工作也会有犯罪记录。
I do not know anything
我什么都不知道
I just heard you say you were from Jeonju
我刚听你说你是全州人
Me too, I go to Jeonju Girls' High School
我也是，我就读全州女子高中
take it
拿去
smoke one
抽一根
Asking a fellow countryman to smoke a cigarette is just a token of appreciation
请同胞抽烟只是表示谢意
I rarely say this
我很少说这个
You know we asked your friends too
你知道我们也问过你的朋友
Everyone says Bong-joo, you are the boss
每个人都说奉珠，你是老板
Not true?
不对？
Can't you go home and sleep?
你就不能回家睡觉吗？
Yes, my parents moved to Yishan
是的，我父母搬到宜山了
So I have to move out
所以我必须搬出去
Then please go take a shower
那么请去洗澡
Washed in the morning
早上洗的
That was yesterday morning
那是昨天早上
What the hell, it's still morning anyway
管他呢，反正现在还是早上
Very hungry
饿极了
Hello
你好
Is it you who knocks 2473?
敲2473是你吗？
Hello, Yingbi, this is Liu Yizhen.
Hello, Yingbi, this is Liu Yizhen.
Junmo's wife
君莫的妻子
Yi Zhen, hello
Yi Zhen, hello
How is it going?
最近好吗？
I'm fine, thank you for your concern
我很好，谢谢你的关心
There is no news about Junmo from yesterday to now
昨天到现在都没有君墨的消息
I'm a little worried
我有点担心
What?
什么？
What's wrong?
怎么了？
He had an asthma attack and called in sick.
他哮喘发作并请了病假。
So hot
很热
To listen to the message please click
收听留言请点击
Is it me, busy?
是我吗，忙吗？
I know you have asthma, can we still have a meal together, right?
我知道你有哮喘， 我们还能一起吃顿饭吗？
that…
那…
My friend is in a hurry. I'll go have a meal and come back.
我的朋友很着急。我去吃个饭再回来。
It's only a woman
这只是一个女人
It's a woman
这是一个女人
OK, who is it?
好吧，是谁？
Going on a double date with my girlfriend?
和女朋友去双重约会？
Handsome ones are the most popular
帅的才是最受欢迎的
I don't eat instant noodles
我不吃方便面
Yes, it’s better to eat with a woman
是的，和女人一起吃饭更好
I can eat instant noodles alone
我一个人就能吃方便面
Yi Zhen, I'm sorry for not telling you earlier.
怡珍，很抱歉没有早点告诉你。
Say it now
现在就说
What are you doing these days?
这些天你在做什么？
Who bought you a suit without letting your wife know?
谁给你买了一套西装而不让你妻子知道？
you misunderstood
你误会了
To tell you the truth, I want to catch drug smugglers.
说实话，我想抓捕毒品走私犯。
Just go undercover and join the gang.
只要去卧底并加入帮派即可。
they really said that
他们确实这么说过
What a nonsense
真是胡说八道
Hello
你好
Chenghao
Chenghao
-Yes -What are you doing?
-是的 -你在做什么？
Just eating with friends
刚和朋友一起吃饭
Wait, I saw her in high school
等等，我在高中时见过她
Didn't expect to see you here
没想到会在这里见到你
haven't seen you for a long time
好久没见到你了
She is my friend from elementary school
她是我小学的朋友
We used to learn Taekwondo together
我们曾经一起学跆拳道
Who is this…
这是谁…
I recently joined the company as president
我最近加入公司担任总裁
Really?
真的吗？
Qi Tie is a junior classmate of my high school church.
齐铁是我高中教会的三年级同学。
Are you OK?
你还好吗？
Very good, thank you for your concern
非常好，谢谢您的关心
How are the police doing?
警察怎么样？
Did you hear that?
你听到了吗？
Which subject are you in?
你属于哪个科目？
Seoul Metropolitan Police Agency Security Section
首尔地方警察厅保安课
Have you finished eating?
你吃完了吗？
Finished
完成的
Can I take Chenghao away?
Can I take Chenghao away?
I'm leaving. I'll call you later.
我走了。我一会打给你。
How dare you meet with the policeman, bastard
你怎么敢去见警察啊混蛋
you misunderstood
你误会了
We have had a good relationship since elementary school
我们从小学起关系就很好
My dad is a poisonous insect
我的爸爸是毒虫
If he takes drugs, he will beat me
如果他吸毒，他就会打我
I used to hide in her house
我曾经躲在她家
Why are you contacting her, asshole?
你为什么要联系她，混蛋？
Go away
离开
I didn't contact her
我没有联系她
It was she who contacted me first
是她先联系我的
Why did that female police officer contact you?
那个女警察为什么联系你？
My dad was caught taking drugs
我爸爸吸毒被抓
Now being held in the police station
目前被关押在派出所
boss
老板
I really do not know
我真的不知道
You will meet Yi Zhen
你会遇见以真
Do you have to blame me for this?
这事你一定要怪我吗？
Let's go
我们走吧
-Chenghao -Yes
-Chenghao -Yes
Have some respect for the boss, you bastard
尊重一下老板吧，你这个混蛋
sorry
对不起
It's me Yi Zhen
It's me Yi Zhen
Do you all know about Jun Mo’s drug investigation case?
你们都知道君莫毒品调查案吗？
Chenghao, do you think I will believe you?
成浩，你觉得我会相信你吗？
I hate notes
我讨厌笔记
enough
足够的
you need to know
你得知道
A cousin suddenly appeared in Taihu
太湖突然出现表弟
His neighbor happens to be…
他的邻居恰好是……
Oldest friend from high school church
高中教会最老的朋友
Don't you think it's strange?
你不觉得很奇怪吗？
South Korea is really small, isn’t it?
韩国真的很小，不是吗？
Qi Tie, where does she and you like the spicy fried rice cake?
齐铁，你和她喜欢哪里的辣炒年糕？
I think so
我想是这样
She is his first love, they do everything together
她是他的初恋情人，他们做什么事都在一起
It's a necklace given by the high school church.
这是高中教会赠送的项链。
should take it home
应该把它带回家
Subtitle translation: Li Yi
字幕翻译：李毅